http://www.fashionweeknews.com/privacy/

HomeFashion DictionaryFashion Designer Career Profile
Browse: Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART CookieGoogle, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Fashion Week News has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal InformationWhen visiting Fashion Week News, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to third party WebsitesWe have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy StatementThe contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Fashion Week News then you may contact us at info+AT+fashionweeknews.com
This privacy policy was generated by the Easy Privacy Policy plugin for WordPress.
Last updated Fri, 20 Nov 2009 03:55
Share
Warning:
Illegal string offset 'echo' in /home/ladymjet/webapps/wp_fwn/wp-content/themes/hybrid/library/extensions/custom-field-series.php on line 82
Comments are closed, but trackbacks and pingbacks are open.
Fashion Design ResourcesFashion Design SchoolsBecome a Fashion DesignerFashion Week CategoriesFashion Design SchoolsFashion Designer BiographyFashion DesignersFashion DictionaryFashion FindsAppel & FrankLondon Fashion WeekendMax & ChloeNet-A-PorterFashion MagazinesFashion ModelsFashion NewsFashion WeekBerlin Fashion WeekLondon Fashion WeekLos Angeles Fashion WeekMilan Fashion WeekNew York Fashion WeekParis Fashion WeekSan Francisco Fashion WeekFitness & Wellness
Recent PostsParis Fashion Week Schedule, January 2013: Haute Couture Collections for Spring/Summer 2013Schedule for Menswear Collections for Fall/Winter 2013 at Paris Fashion WeekParis Fashion Week Schedule for Spring 2012 CollectionsLondon Fashion Week Schedule for Spring 2012 CollectionsNew York Fashion Week Schedule for the Spring 2012 CollectionsRodarte Label Designs Costumes for Aronofsky’s “Black Swan”Jimmy Choo Re-Launches Men’s Footwear LineDefinitive Paris Fashion Week Schedule for September-October 2010Updated Paris Fashion Week Schedule, September 28th – October 6th, 2010Paris Fashion Week Schedule for Spring/Summer 2011 Collections — Subject to ChangeLondon Fashion Week Schedule for Spring/Summer 2011 CollectionsRunway Shows Stream Live During New York Fashion WeekNew York Fashion Week September Schedule for Spring/Summer 2011 CollectionsLindsay Lohan's Fashion Designer Debut for Emanuel Ungaro PannedLondon Fashion Weekend September 2009 Tickets and PricesParis Fashion Week Dates and Schedule Spring 2010 Ready-to-Wear CollectionsNew York Fashion Week Presents Rouge Tomate Juice BarLondon Fashion Weekend September 24-27, 2009Fashion’s Night Out NYC, September 10, 2009New York Fashion Week Runway Experience Presented By Phillip Lim and American Express
Fashion Week News ArchivesJanuary 2013September 2011December 2010September 2010October 2009September 2009August 2009July 2009May 2009April 2009March 2009February 2009January 2009December 2008November 2008October 2008June 2008March 2008February 2008January 2008December 2007November 2007October 2007September 2007August 2007July 2007May 2007April 2007March 2007February 2007January 2007December 2006October 2006September 2006August 2006July 2006June 2006May 2006
More InformationAbout UsPrivacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 Fashion Week News.
Powered by WordPress and Hybrid.
